MAHI CHAURASIA

SKILLS

With a keen research interest, I have developed skills in report writing, analysis of information, and data collection alongside critical thinking, and analysis of the material. With multiple internships and work experience throughout, I have honed my creative thinking skills, excelled in verbal and written communication, and developed **content writing and copywriting skills** with **SEO optimization** knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

Adviso, Remote - Website Content Writer

SEPTEMBER 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

- Adviso is a comprehensive partner in the world of finance and business solutions offering a bunch of services like Investment Banking, Management Consultancy, etc.
- My main job was to write content for Adviso's website with SEO optimization.

Plus- India's first jewelry savings app, Remote - Copywriter/Content Creator

AUGUST 2023 - SEPTEMBER 2023

- India's first savings app for gold jewelry.
- I was responsible for creating memes and writing long-form as well as short-form content.

Decoralley, Delhi — Content Creation Intern

JANUARY 2022 - FEBRUARY 2022

• An e-commerce platform that crosses all boundaries and connects artists to buyers across the globe.

ENACTUS, SRCASW - Copywriter/ Content Writer

DECEMBER 2020 - DECEMBER 2021

- An organization where sustainable solutions are created to modern world problems.
- Involved in the process of writing product descriptions, and creating copy for the banners.

ICSSR project: Ecological Feminism of Indian Women, a Comprehensive Study on Indigenous Practices for Sustainable Development — Copywriter/ Content Writer

SEPTEMBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

• This project gives a golden opportunity to connect with some great women environmental conservationists. With the help of a dialogue series conducted every Friday, a new insight is gained into the life of some creative, passionate, and hardworking women.

Udayan Care — Research Intern

MAY 2022 - JULY 2022

• The internship was based on research about how the residential care model affects the physical and mental health of children so that appropriate measures can be taken to improve mental health services in the future. This research was conducted by the students of Duke University in collaboration with Udayan Care.

EDUCATION

Shaheed Rajguru College of Applied Sciences For Women, DU - BA (Hons) Psychology

2020- 2023, Delhi

Undergraduate in Psychology with honors from Delhi University. The main areas of interest are research, clinical psychology, and social psychology.